ANDRII DOVHANIUK JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

+380 660745969 dovhaniuk.andriy@gmail.com Telegram LinkedIn GitHub Kyiv, Ukraine

Summary

Frontend developer with a strong analytical mindset. Responsible, punctual and motivated individual who is always willing to learn and gain new experience. Motivated to continually develop and improve my skills. The ability to find solutions to any problem is also one of my strengths. Friendly team player, always willing to help.

Project experience

- Messenger (Page , Code) Individual project. Chat app with user authorisation, user search, ability to send messages, photos. Stack: HTML/SASS, React, Firebase Auth/Firestore
- Simple Phonebook(Page ,Code) Individual project. Phonebook app with user authorisation, user filter, ability to add/remove user, connected to Swagger backend API. Stack: HTML, React, Redux Toolkit, MUI.
- Movies(Page, Code) Individual project. Movies base app with recent movies, movie search, movie details, connected to themoviedb.org. Stack: HTML, React, Styled Components, Axios, REST API
- ✓ Bookshelf (Page , Code) Team project. A website with a responsive layout, included auth, filterd by cathegory, add book to shopping-list. Role: SCRUM Master, developer, header/modal/authorization/backend connections. Stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Vite, REST API, Firebase
- Search media (Page , Code) Individual project. A website with a responsive layout for search photo/video on Pixabay.com, included search via tags. Stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, REST API, Parcel
- ✓ Yacht Adventures (Page, Code) Team project. A website with a pesponsive layout. Role: SCRUM Master, developer, gallery section/page animations. Stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Vite

Hard skills

HTML/CSS/SASS, Responsive/Adaptive Design, JavaScript/TypeScript, REST API, GIT, React, Redux, Zustand, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Firebase, Parcel/Vite/Webpack

Soft skills

Team work, Problem solving, Strong adaptation skills, High analytics skills, Communicative

Work experience

2023/03 - present

Frontend Developer

Freelancer

- ✓ HTML, CSS, JS, React
- √ time managment
- ✓ team working
- ✓ communication

2012/10 - 2023/03

Chief Specialist of the Automated System Administration and Computer Technologies Department

Kyiv Court of Appeal

- ✓ communication with clients,
- ✓ study and analysis of new technologies,
- ✓ implementation,
- √ development of documentation,
- ✓ personnel training,
- ✓ identification and elimination of technical problems

Education

2024/05

IT School GoIT

JavaScript fullstack developer (May 2023 - March 2024)

2002/09

Taras Shevchenko National University of Kyiv

Associate's degree, Justice (September 2002 - July 2007)

Languages

English - advanced Ukrainian - native Russian - native